Guide to the United Faculty and Pitt Professional Union Records, 1970-1995 AIS.1988.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Miscellaneous Materials (Box 16, Folder 34)
- University of Pittsburgh Review, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- American Federation of Teachers (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Merit Raise Distribution, Faculty and Staff, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- American Federation of Teachers Albert Einstein Poster (Oversize 1)